Mom, would you relax?
엄마, 그만 해요
거긴 여기서 멀고 여자 혼자
밤에 다니다 당했대요
That was 10 blocks from here,
and she was walking alone at night.
I would never do that.
난 안 그래요
그러니까 걱정 말아요
Mom, come on, stop worrying.
This is a safe street. This is
a safe building. There's nothing
우리 아파트는 안전해서
그런 강도가...
Oh, my God! What are
you doing in here?!
어머!
Mom, I gotta go! IT gotta go!
엄마, 끊어요!
맙소사...
Oh, my God!
알았어
신문을 보고 싶었구나
That's fine, you just read the paper.
난 냄비를 가져올게
너 때리려는 거 아냐
I'm gonna get a pot.
It's not for you.
Okay, that's fine.
이제 됐다!
Read the Family Circus...
가족 얘기도 읽고
'유머 한마디'도 읽어
...enjoy the gentle comedy....
어머, 어째, 세상에나!
Oh, my God, my God, my God, my God....
It's open, you guys.
열렸어!
안녕하세요?
누구시죠?
Can I help you?
피비 아직 여기 살아요?
Does Phoebe still live here?
아뇨, 하지만 메시지는
전해 줄 수 있어요
No, she doesn't. But I can get
a message to her.
잘됐네요
Great. Just tell her
her husband stopped by.
남편이 들렀다고 전해 줘요
남편?
Her what?
그 마술은 어떻게 하죠?
How did you do that?
The One With Phoebe's Husband
믿을 수가 없어, 피비
결혼했단 말이야?
This is unbelievable, Pheebs.
How can you be married?
정식으로 결혼한 게 아냐
I'm not "married"
married, you know?
게이 친구인데
캐나다에서 왔거든
He's just a friend, and he's gay...
...and he was from Canada,
and he needed a Green Card.
영주권을 얻어 주려고
던칸과 결혼하다니!
I can't believe you married Duncan!
나랑 같이 살면서도
감쪽같이 숨겼어?
How could you not tell me?
We told each other everything.
네가 선입견을 가지고
반대할까 봐서
I'm sorry, but I knew if I told you,
you'd get judgmental...
...and wouldn't approve.
Of course I wouldn't approve!
당연하지!
그 남자는 게이란 말야!
너 정신이 있니?
You were totally in love
with this guy who, hello, was gay.
What the hell were you thinking?
See? And you thought
she'd be judgmental.
피비 예상이 적중했군
사랑한 게 아니라
친구를 도운 것뿐이야
I wasn't in love with him.
I was helping out a friend.
던칸이 떠나고
한 달 동안 시름했잖아
When he left town, you
stayed in your pajamas for a month.
치즈버거도 먹었고!
And I saw you eat a cheeseburger.
안 그래?
Well, didn't you?
I might have.
먹었을지도 몰라
내게 숨기다니!
I can't believe you didn't tell me.
그러는 넌?
Like you tell me everything?
내가 뭘 숨겼는데?
What have I not told you?
글쎄...
I don't know.
The fact that the underwear out
on the telephone pole is yours...
전신주에 걸린 팬티는
네가 바비와 발코니에서
일 내다가 벗은 거잖아!
...from when you had sex
with Bobby on the terrace!
What?
잠깐만!
누구한테 들었어?
Wait a minute! Who told you?
You are dead meat.
넌 죽은목숨이야!
그게 비밀이었던가?
I didn't know it was a big secret.
아냐, 비밀은 무슨
Oh, it's not big. Not at all.
IKind of the same as, say...
뭐라고 할까...
젖꼭지 세 개인 남자!
... I don't know, having
a third nipple!
젖꼭지가 세 개야?
You have a third nipple?
You bitch!
나쁜 계집!
Whip it out! Whip it out!
- 벗어! 벗어!
- 그만둬!
There's nothing to see! It's a
tiny bump. It's totally useless.
작은 물혹일 뿐이야
쓸모도 없다고
그럼 다른 두 젖꼭지는
용도가 많은가 보지?
As opposed to your other
multi-functional nipples?
챈들러, 너 너무했어
내겐 혹이라면서!
I can't believe you!
You told me it was a nubbin.
Joey, what did you think
a nubbin was?
넌 뭐라고 생각했는데?
You see something, you hear a word,
I thought that's what it was.
본인이 그렇다기에
그냥 믿었지
-Let me see it again!
-Yes, show us your nubbin!
- 다시 보여 줘
- 그래, 혹을 보여 줘!
안 돼!
조이는 포르노에 출연했어!
Joey was in a porno movie!
If I'm going down,
I'm taking everybody with me!
나 혼자만 당할 순 없지
내가 총 맞았냐?
- 맙소사!
- 정말 포르노를 찍었어?
-Oh, my God!
-You were in a porno?!
일거리가 필요했거는
먹고는 살아야지
I was young and I just wanted a job.
But I couldn't go through with it.
한데 도저히 못하겠더라
복사기 수리공 역이었는데
They let me be the guy who fixes
the copier but can't...
...because there's people
having sex on it.
위에서 섹스를 해서
복사기는 못 고쳤어
That is wild!
변태네!
-What's it shaped like?
-ls it hairy?
- 어떻게 생겼어?
- 털도 났어?
손으로 퉁기면 어때?
What happens if you flick it?
So does it do anything,
you know, special?
특별한 기능이라도 있어?
Pressing my third nipple
opens the delivery entrance...
그럼, 그 젖꼭지를 누르면
마법의 세계로 통하는
비밀의 문이 열리거든
...to the magical land of Narnia.
어떤 문화권에선 정력의
상징으로도 통해요
In some cultures, having a third nipple
is actually a sign of virility.
You get the best huts,
and women dance naked around you.
여자들이 벌거벗고
집 주위를 빙글빙글 돌죠
미국에도 그런 곳 있어요?
Are any of these cultures,
per chance, in the Tri-State area?
You know, you are so amazing.
Is there anything you don't know?
정말 대단해
자기가 모르는 건 없어?
'줄리는 똑똑해
줄리는 특별해'
Julie's so smart!
Julie's so special!
I wanted you to hook up
with Ross as much as you did.
나도 네가 로스와
사귀기를 바랬었지만
But he's with her now.
You'll have to get over it.
지금은 줄리 애인이잖아
그만 잊어버려
그래, 잊어야겠지
Oh, I'm going to have to get over it.
바로 그거였구나
잊으면 되는 거였어!
I didn't know that's what I had to do.
I just have to get over it.
- 멋진데!
- 어디 좋은 데 가요?
-Sassy lady!
-Where are you going?
밤에 던칸 만나요
지금 스케이트 타거든요
I'm meeting Duncan.
He's skating tonight at the Garden.
He's in the Capades.
아이스 댄싱 단원이라서
-The lce Capades?
-No, the Gravel Capades.
- 얼음에서?
- 아니, 자갈밭에서
회전은 잘 안 되지만
넘어지면 엄청 재밌지
The turns aren't as fast,
but when Snoopy falls? Funny.
I can't believe
you'd dress up for him.
그 남자 만나는데
이렇게 차려입어?
You're setting yourself up
all over again.
또 빠져들면 어쩌려고
Okay, no.
아냐!
For your information, I'm seeing him
so I can put those feelings behind me.
그를 만나서 옛 감정을
잊어 버리려는 거야
The reason I'm dressed like this
is because I think it's nice...
이렇게 차려입는 건...
게이 남편에게 잘 보여서
나쁠 것 없잖아?
...to look nice for your gay husband.
이런, 우유가 없네
Darn it, we're all out of milk.
Chandler, will you fill me up here?
챈들러, 우유 좀 줄래?
아, 세 번째 젖꼭지로
짜 달란 말이군
I see, I see. Because of
the third-nipple thing.
나중에 봐
Okay, sweetie, I'll see you later.
- 갈게
- 안녕
-See you later, Rach.
-Bye-bye, Julie.
- 나중에 봐요, 레이첼
- 빠빠이, 줄리
야!
Come on, cut it out!
그만 해!
- 레이첼
- 왜?
-Can I ask you something?
-Sure.
뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
그럼
- 아냐
- 뭔데?
What?
- 아냐
- 어서 말해 봐
Come on, talk to me.
좋아
What's the longest you've been
in a relationship before...
남자친구를 사귀면서
가장 늦게...
... having the sex?
관계한 게 얼마만이야?
그건 왜?
혹시 줄리하고...
Why? Who's not?
Are you and Julie not?
줄리하고 관계 안 해?
Are you and Julie not having sex?
정식 관계라면...
안 해
Technically?
No.
Is it because she's so cold in bed?
잠자리에서 목석이라?
아님 무슨 선생님처럼
딱딱거려?
Or because she's kind of bossy,
makes it feel like school?
아냐, 그렇지 않아
스킨십은 지금도 하거든
No! She's great. And it's not
like we haven't done anything.
여러 가지를 하는데
예를 들면...
We do plenty of other stuff.
Lots of other stuff like
아냐, 듣고 싶지 않아!
No! Don't need to know the details.
뭐랄까...
내 문제인 것 같아
No, it's just....
It's me.
I've only been with
one woman my whole life...
지금껏 한 여자하고만
그걸 해봤는데
레즈비언이 돼버렸잖아
...and she turned out to be a lesbian.
So now I've got myself
all psyched out.
그 후로는 엄두가 안 나
그 생각이 머릿속에
박혀서는...
It's become, like, this...
...this thing!
내가 한심하지?
You must just think I'm weird.
No, I don't think it's weird.
아냐, 한심하긴 네가 뭘
I think, in fact....
- 내 생각 말해 줄까?
- 뭔데?
-ln fact, you know what I think?
-What?
내가 보기엔 섹시해
I think it's sexy.
Sexy?
섹시?
여자 입장에서 말하는데
Let me tell you something.
As a woman...
...there is nothing sexier...
섹스를 원하지 않는 남자가
얼마나 섹시하다고
...than a man who does not
want to have sex.
No kidding?
정말?
- 난 어쩌는 줄 알아?
- 어쩌는데?
You know what I'd do?
난 기다려
I'd wait.
-You'd wait?
-Absolutely. I would wait...
기다린다고?
그럼, 기다리고
또 기다리고...
...and wait....
Then I'd wait some more.
그리곤 더 기다린다고
정말?
Really?
줄리가 자길 안아 달라고
매달리고 애원하면서
I don't care if she tells you
she wants it, she begs, she pleads...
...she tells you she's gonna
have sex with another man
다른 남자랑 자겠다고
엄포를 놓으면
효과가 있다는 뜻이야
That just means it's working.
여자가 그걸 원한다고?
Women really want this?
More than jewelry.
보석보다 더 원하지
매디슨 스퀘어 가든
피비!
쨘!
- 어서 와
- 반가워
Look at you! You look great!
신수 훤한데!
Do l? Thank you.
그래? 고마워
So do you. Sparkly!
- 너도, 눈이 부실 정도야
- 고마워
아이스 댄싱 단원으로
정말 출세했네
This is pretty wonderful,
Mr. Major Capades Guy!
I remember when you were just
King Friday in Mr. Roger's Ice Is Nice.
예전엔 '얼음은 좋아'
이런 것에만 나오더니
You always said I'd make it.
내가 성공할 거라고 했잖아
Well, you know,
I'm kind of spooky that way.
난 점쟁이 기질이 있거든
Gosh, I missed you!
보고 싶었어
-I'm gonna get changed.
-Okay.
- 옷 갈아입고 올게
- 알았어
지금
Now.
참, 알았어
Oh! Right. Okay.
- '올레이'!
- 뭐?
Ole!
What?
외투 멋지다고
The Matador....
올레이!
Ole!
Sweetie, can you
hold this for a second?
이것 잠깐 들어 줄래?
- 알았어
- 고마워
줄리?
얼굴에 고생물 학자가
들러붙었어요
Sorry, you had a
paleontologist on your face.
걱정 말아요
떨어지고 없으니까
But it's gone now.
You're all right.
Hi, everyone.
- 어서들 와
- 안녕
아까 조언해 줘서 고마워
I wanted to thank you
for our little talk before.
No problem! So you're gonna
go with the waiting thing?
뭘 그런 것 같고
기다리기로 작정했어?
그러려고 했는데
조이 말은 틀리더라고
I was going to, but after
I talked to you, I talked to Joey.
Good. What did he say?
조이는 뭐래?
과거는 다 잊고
일단 질러 보라고
He told me to get over myself
and just do it.
너와 조이의 말을
비교해 보니까
I thought about what you said
and about what he said.
조이의 말을 들으면
섹스 할 수 있겠더라
And his way, I get
to have sex tonight, so....
주머니에 뭐가 들었지?
What is this in my pocket?
조이의 포르노!
Why, it's Joey's porno movie!
Pop it in!
틀어 봐
난 괜찮아
I'm fine, if you're
okay watching a video...
젖꼭지 두 개인 사람만
나오는데 괜찮겠어?
...filled with two-nippled people.
포르노 영화라...
심장에 불만 지르누만
People having sex.
That's just what I need to see.
섹스인데 뭐 어때서?
What's wrong with people having sex?
그게...
포르노는 혐오스럽고
여자들을 격하시키고
Well, you know, these
movies are offensive...
...and degrading
to women and females....
항상 시뻘건 불빛들만
흔들거리고...
And the lighting's
always unflattering.
모니카, 좀 도와 줄래?
-Monica, help me out here.
-Hell, I wanna see Joey!
난 조이 보고 싶어!
So is there a story?
Or do they just start doing it right
내용은 있어요?
아님 처음부터 무조건...
Oh. Never mind.
됐어요
저런 타이핑 테스트는
난생 처음 봤어
Wait a minute. That is the craziest
typing test I've ever seen.
직장은 따 놓은 당상이야
All I say is, she'd
better get the job.
Looks to me like he's
the one getting the job.
여자는 일하고
남자는 소리만 지르네
나온다!
Here I come.
See, I'm coming to fix the copier.
복사기를 고치러 왔는데
고칠 수가 없어서
고심하다가...
I can't get to the copier.
I'm thinking, "What do I do?"
So I just watch them have sex.
저들이 하는 것을
구경하기로 했지
그리곤 이렇게 말하지
Then I say Here's my line!
You know, that's bad
for the paper tray.
'용지 받침대 부서지겠어요'
- 멋졌어, 친구
- 고마워
Nice work, my friend!
Wait, you see me again. Hang on,
the guy's butt's blocking me.
잠깐, 또 나올 거야
남자 엉덩이에 가렸네
There I am. There I am.
There I am....
저 때 나오고
저기서도 나오고...
So what's up?
You came to see me yesterday.
무슨 일이야?
어제 날 보러 왔었다며?
그래
말할게
이혼해야 될 것 같아서
I kind of need a divorce.
O...
어... 그랬구나
... kay.
How come?
이유는?
Actually, I'm getting married again.
결혼상대를 만났거든
뭐라고?
What?
I don't know how to tell you this.
어떻게 말해야 할지...
I'm straight.
난 게이가 아냐
놀랄 만도 해
말도 안 돼!
게이가 아니라니?
I don't understand.
How can you be straight?
You're so smart and funny...
넌 똑똑하고 웃기고
...and you throw
such great Academy Award parties!
멋진 아카데미상 파티도
매년 열었잖아!
That's what I kept telling myself.
나도 많이 고심했어
But you reach a point
where you can't live a lie anymore.
하지만 더는 거짓된 삶을
살 수가 없겠더라고
안 지 얼마나 됐지?
How long have you known?
정상일지 모른다는
생각은 항상 했어
I guess on some level
I always knew I was straight.
난 내가 호모인 줄 알았어!
I thought I was supposed
to be something else.
난 아이스 댄서고
친구들도 모두 게이잖아!
I'm an ice dancer, all my friends
are gay. I was just trying to fit in.
여자를 만났단 말이야?
And there's actually a woman?
Her name's Debra.
이름은 데브라야
함께 잠자리를 한 첫 여자야?
Well, is she the first
that you've been with?
I've never told you this...
이 말은 안 했었지만
대학 때 두어 번...
... but there were one
or two times back in college when...
술 취해 아침에 일어나면
옆에 여자가 누워 있었어
... I'd get drunk,
go to a straight bar...
...and wake up with
a woman next to me.
술에 취했었고
대학은 실험적인 곳이잖아!
I told myself it was the liquor,
and everyone experiments in college.
Sure.
그랬겠지
나도 선택의 여지가 없어
이렇게 태어난 걸 어째?
Now I know I don't have a choice.
I was born this way!
I don't know what to say.
달리 할 말이 없네
6년 동안 남편이었다는
작자가 절규하잖아
You're married to someone for
six years and you think you know him.
'난 게이가 아니다! '
And then one day he says,
"Oh, I'm not gay!"
난 예전 그대로야
I'm still me.
Why couldn't you just have
figured this out six years ago?
왜 6년 전에는 그렇게
느끼지 못했지?
아직도 원숭이 냄새가 나
You know, it still
smells like monkey in there.
궁금증이 이제야 풀렸군
That saves us the conversation.
저녁 고마웠어
난 피곤해 죽겠어
This has been great,
but I'm officially wiped.
- 나도, 그만 가자
- 안 돼!
Me too. We should get going.
이렇게 갈 순 없어!
No! Come on, you guys!
겨우 11시 반이잖아
Come on, it's only 1 1 :30.
대화를 하자고
대화한 지도 오래됐잖아
Let's just talk. We never just
hang out and talk anymore.
레이첼, 만나면 수다인데?
Rachel, that's all we do.
우리는 그렇지만
줄리는?
Maybe that's all we do.
What about Julie?
내가 뭘요?
우리랑 알게 된 지도
두 달이 돼가는데
You have been in our lives
for nearly two months now...
우린 줄리를 잘 몰라요
...and we don't really know you.
줄리가 대체 누구죠?
I mean, who is Julie?
좋아하는 건 뭐고
싫어하는 건 뭐죠?
What do you like?
What don't you like?
We want to know everything.
당신에 대해 말해 줘요
시작하면 끝이 없어요
Well, that could take awhile.
So?
그래서요?
이중에 줄리에 대해
알고 싶지 않는 사람?
Who here does not have
the time to get to know Julie?
- 나 시간 많아
- 나도 한가해
I got the time to get to know Julie.
난 줄리를 잘 아니까
가도 되겠지?
I know her pretty well.
Can I go?
알았어
That's fine.
유년시절부터 시작하죠
어떻게 컸어요?
Let's start with your childhood.
What was that like?
In a nutshell
한마디로 말하면...
So, have you told your parents?
부모님께는 말했어?
No, but it'll be okay.
They're pretty cool.
아니, 하지만 괜찮아
이해해 주실 거야
형도 정상이거든
My brother's straight, so....
여기
Here you go.
You know what?
I just have one more question.
하나만 더 물어볼게
자기가 일찍 알아챘고
내가 곁에 있었다면
If you had figured this out sooner,
and I had been around...
...do you think l
would have been the one...?
만에 하나로도 나와...
아냐, 대답하지 마
달라질 것도 없으니까
No. Don't tell me.
I don't think either answer
would make me feel better. Here.
여기
사랑해, 피비
I love you, Phoebe.
형이 정상이라고?
So your brother's straight, huh?
Seriously.
난 심각해
2학년 담임은
토마스 선생님이었고
and my second-grade teacher
was Miss Thomas...
1학년 담임은
콥 선생님이었어요
...and my first-grade teacher
was Mrs. Cobb.
곱 선생님?
Mrs. Gobb?
No, Cobb. Like cobb salad.
아뇨, 콥 선생님이요
샐러드 이름과 같죠
콥 샐러드엔 뭐가 들었죠?
What exactly is in a cobb salad?
- 난 갈래!
- 왜?
I'm going home.
줄리 말 엄청 많지?
Boy, that Julie's a talker, huh?
잘 자
Good night.
시간이 많이 흘렀는데
설마 지금...
It's pretty late. You're
probably not still planning on....
당연히 해야지
No, I am.
긴장돼?
Are you nervous?
아니, 첫 여자도 아닌데 뭘
I have done it before.
어떻게 할 건데?
I mean, how are
you gonna handle it?
Are you gonna talk about it beforehand?
Are you just gonna pounce?
하자고 말할 거야?
아님 그냥 눕힐 거야?
글쎄, 어떻게 될지는
들어가 봐야지
I don't know. I guess
I'm just gonna...
...see what happens.
알았어, 행운을 빌어
Good luck!
- 왜?
- 아무것도 아냐
What?
처음으로 관계를 갖는데
Nothing....
It is your first time with her,
and if the first time doesn't go well...
처음부터 삐걱거리면
회복 불능이잖아
...well then, that's pretty darn
hard to recover from.
나 긴장돼
Okay, now I'm nervous.
Maybe you should put it off.
- 나중에 하면 되잖아
- 그건 싫어!
No, I don't want to put it off!
미치겠네!
I spent last year being
so unbelievably miserable.
난 작년에 독수공방으로
외롭게 보냈어
한데 지금은 행복해
And now I'm actually happy.
날아갈 듯 행복하다고
You know, I mean really happy.
관계를 망치긴 싫어
무슨 말인지 알아?
I just don't wanna....
I don't wanna mess it up, you know?
알아
I know.
미안해
I'm sorry.
- 네 잘못도 아니잖아
- 맞아
It's not your fault.
Right.
Maybe it doesn't
have to be this tough.
힘들어할 것 없어
여자들은 즉흥적이고
자연적인 걸 좋아해
Maybe you were on the right track
with that whole "spontaneous" thing.
-Women really like that.
-Really?
- 정말?
- 응!
- 나라면...
- 뭐?
I mean if it were me,
I'd want you to....
네가 날 부서져라 안고
키스를 하는 거야
I don't know, catch me off guard
with a really...
...good kiss.
처음엔 부드럽고...
Really sort of soft at first.
머리카락을 쓸어 올려주고
And then maybe brush
the hair away from my face.
And then look far into my eyes...
내 눈을 들여다보면서
행복한 일을 미리
알려주는 듯이
...in a way that lets me
know something...
...amazing is about to happen.
그리고?
그리곤 날 잡아당겨서
서로 몸을 밀착시키고
And then, I don't know, then...
...you'd pull me
really close to you so that...
...so that I'd be pressed up
right against you.
그 다음엔...
서로 땀을 흘리면서
And it would get kind of...
...sweaty...
눈앞은 희미해지고
...and blurry.
행복을 누리는 거지
And then it's just happening.
고마워, 레이첼
잘 자
Thanks, Rach. Good night!
맙소사!
Oh, God!
좋은 아침!
Good morning!
어젯밤에 홍콩 갔다왔나?
Well, somebody got some last night!
Twice!
두 번이나요!